# Dinh Ky Le

Vietnam



ldky90@gmail.com



(+84)969436154



linkedin.com/in/le-dinh-ky

# **Summary**

Hello, I am a Senior Fullstack Engineer with extensive experience in the field of Information Technology. I have strong programming skills with popular languages such as Javascript, Golang, and PHP, and experience using popular frameworks such as React, NextJS, and Laravel.

Having worked as a Technical Lead previously, I possess leadership and project management experience in addition to my technical expertise. I have developed processes and selected suitable technology solutions for products, ensuring efficient deployment and successful delivery in accordance with project plans.

In previous positions, I have provided unique technical solutions that meet customer needs, guided and trained team members to develop their skills and knowledge, and contributed to high-performing teams by fostering positive working relationships.

I am enthused by new challenges and love exploiting my experience and skill set to collaborate with individuals and organizations alike. If you are searching for a Senior Fullstack Engineer with diversity in skills and a wealth of experience, please contact me for further information.

## **Experience**



## Lead Frontend Engineer

Treehouse

2021 - Present (2 years)

Products:

- Company: https://treehouse.finance
- Harvest: https://harvest.treehouse.finance
- Institutions: https://institutions.treehouse.finance
- Gaia: https://gaia.treehouse.finance
- Internal Dashboard

Team size: 30 Responsibilities:

- Led the Frontend team and built a process for teamwork
- Communicate with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, and PMs on a daily basis
- Researching and deciding on a platform, technical solutions, and structure for the project
- Reviewing code, doing workshops for training, and sharing knowledge with team members

# ™ Software Engineer

**TESO** 

2019 - 2021 (2 years)

Products:

- Build to rent: https://buildtorent.io/
- Blog: https://blog.buildtorent.io/

- Agency & Customer Dashboard

Team size: 10 Responsibilities:

- Developed and shipped highly interactive web applications for clients
- Optimized and maintained old projects
- Worked closely with designers and management team to develop, document, and manage



## **SYNOVE Full Stack Engineer**

Synova Solutions

2017 - 2018 (1 year)

- Worked with a variety of different languages, platforms, frameworks, and content management
- Architected and implemented the front-end from designs



## Freelance Web Developer

Freelancer.com

2014 - 2016 (2 years)

- Started to work in the position of web developer. The first time to develop a website in PHP language programming
- Developed and maintained code for client websites primarily using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress
- Manually tested sites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness

#### **Education**



#### **Hue University of Sciences**

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Information Technology

2010 - 2014

Worked at home as a freelance

#### Skills

JavaScript • TypeScript • React.js • Next.js • Redux.js • Tailwind CSS • Unit Testing • Web3 • Vue.js • Express.js